Guide to the Joel B. Levinson Photographs, 1950-2006 AIS.2015.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Personal Copies of "Pittsburgh: Views in the 21st Century", 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Personal Copy of "Pittsburgh: An American City," by Walt Urbina and Sally Webb, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Correspondence and Digital Photos for Publications, ca. 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Correspondence about Publications, ca. 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Prints of Downtown Pittsburgh (Oversize 7-6, Folder 1)